Thank you for watching!
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
The morning chimes have rung, and it's us, the CJB.
Before we begin, I'd like to announce today's mc of the day.
Please cast your votes for one or two, whichever one you prefer, and the mc will be the one holding the numbered card with that number on it.
Let's start voting.
Oh, no.
I'll do it this way.
Rita, first time in the showroom.
Newbie, newbie.
It's okay to look at it, right?
We're good, right?
Vote
Shall we close it?
Four.
One.
Ta-da!
Okay, then.
Which way?
Okay.
Good, because you have a nasal voice.
That's true.
It's hard to hear.
Well, I'm holding the number 2 ticket, so I'm Nakayama, and I'll be your MC today.
I look forward to working with you.
I'm Riko Nakayama, and I'll be your MC today.
And,
Suzuki number lucky 7, Mirei Hoshino. Please give me a hand.
Please do.
Let's begin.
Shrimp in the middle,
Delightful and Fufu Funny Showroom
Thank you very much for visiting the 67th Ebichu's Delightful and Fudgy Showroom today.
Thank you very much.
Ebichu's Delightful and Fufu na Showroom is the sister show of our sister showroom, Ukka's Showroom.
So, it's time to spread the word.
In order to get as many people as possible to watch this distribution, I'm going to make an announcement on Ebichu's Takasu Family X now, so please spread the word.
Manager.
Okay.
Recently, Ebichu's Twitter has sprouted an ego.
The manager says that the name of the person who tweets who is the manager will be written.
What should we do?
Well then,
Hi, Cheese.
Cheese.
Thank you very much.
Please spread the word.
Today is Okie's day.
It's Okie's Imitation Okie, isn't it?
I'm sure Mr. Okki will give it to you,
Please spread the word.
Let's go to the corner now.
Today's project is as follows.
Let's call it
A funny and funny questionnaire talk.
Before I give a talk, I take a questionnaire to decide what I will talk about. That's what a questionnaire talk is.
Do you want to announce the theme?
Yes, I do.
1. Every Mizutori Lucky.
2. Tour coming soon.
3. Nakayama about hair color.
4. Pollen is impossible. Hoshina.
5. Nakayama about white rice being too delicious.
6. Talking Hoshina.
7. Free talk.
We often do this survey talk, don't we?
Usually, the number is decided up to about 5.
Today, there were too many, so we had a free talk at the end.
As for Miyuki-chan, there is a word "chatting" at the stage of 6.
It's a chat.
Miyuki can talk as much as she wants.
That's right.
Which one is good?
Please vote.
Ours is a gal who looks like a gal.
OK.
That's flashy.
We have a lot of subjects for the two of us.
That's right.
Hard on the enhancements?
I still did it today,
Yesterday was tough.
Yesterday was hard,
It was bad yesterday, and it was bad again this morning,
You had a lesson today.
The house dust is already getting worse.
I was like a lady from this morning.
We were going to make a dance routine,
What is she doing? The lesson room is dirty.
I can't deny that.
Until the deadline. 5
Four.
Five, four, three, two, two...
Two.
Done.
What's the most popular number?
Number one?
Oh! Absolutely!
Sweet little Lucky, isn't it?
I knew this one would be chosen.
Why?
Let me tell you why,
Did any of you come here to see this?
I'm a fake fortune teller,
Rittan,
Rittan worships this phony fortune teller?
It's like a shrine,
We were a pair.
In the end, we decided to keep our hair color the same because it was funny.
That's right.
It made me feel like a phony,
Did you go on the first day?
Thank you very much.
It's been a long time since Theatre Shrimp 2024 was held,
It's been about 6 years?
I think it's been about 6 years, maybe 8? No, not really.
It was around the time I graduated from junior high school.
I was around that time too.
That's right. I graduated from high school.
I graduated high school too,
So that's the timing.
That's right,
I was a student at that time,
And March was the hardest time of the year for students with final exams and so on,
I remember how desperate I was during that period,
But now I am an adult, and there are 10 of us.
I did it all over again.
I was a student then, so I played high school girls and so on,
But now we are adults.
Everyone was an adult.
I played a fortune teller who was 30 years old,
I was 23,
My younger sisters also played roles that were older than their actual age,
Like the office worker and Ino.
Office worker and new employee?
I was wearing a suit.
That's right.
Fortune teller. A phony fortune teller.
He's a phony fortune teller, so he's not a regular fortune teller,
Like a fortune teller.
Since ancient times, the Yasuda family has had a sense that you are the children of God,
There is a feeling that the Yasuda family mirrors the watchful mind of you children of the gods, a cold, unbroken sense of the unbroken period.
I had a feeling that you are the children of God, and that you are the children of God,
I was kidding, wasn't I? I was totally fooling around.
I did quite a bit of stage work, and I did a lot of stage work with other people,
And then after that, I had a lot of proper roles on the stage,
That's right. You played a detective, right?
A detective role. That was a little strange, too.
In general, Tsuchiya's stage characters are strange. All of them.
But he seemed to be all things to all people,
He was a fortune teller in front of everyone, and under pressure, he threw up,
But then he would try his best to be a fortune teller in front of everyone, and under the pressure of that, he would throw up.
I really enjoyed it,
It was fun.
Was it fun?
Mr. Tsuchiya told me to throw up a lot, and I did.
I kept repeating it, so my legacy was raised.
Were there any difficulties in playing the role?
Difficulties?
But at first, there was a difference between your idea of a phony fortune teller and my idea of a phony fortune teller,
I thought it would be more interesting,
But then again, Tsuchiya-san is very experienced in the basics of variety,
When I said what he said with the same timing as he said, people laughed so much. I thought he was a genius.
I felt that Tsuchiya-san wrote it,
He does it in this way,
After every performance, I greet the audience.
Katenkohl.
Katen call! And when I looked at Tsuchiya-san's face, he always had a smiling, happy expression on his face,
It was really the most fun.
That's right. It was Mr. Tsuchiya at Urero, too, wasn't it?
I think it was based on the "White Snake Fortune Telling.
Oh, really?
I see.
Katenkohl.
But, as I asked you earlier, is there anyone you used as a model? Like that.
Someone you used as a model?
Yes!
I don't need one.
I had a friend who was a bit of a classy lady, and I used to copy her moves and stuff.
Oh, yeah, she was classy.
Like this.
I was doing it like this.
Is the flat part from the artist?
Yes. He was a writer who couldn't decide for himself what would happen to the main character of his work, so he asked a fortune teller to decide for him.
That's definitely not true. And that's not why he uses fortune-telling.
It's very interesting, isn't it?
That's what Tsuchiya-san is all about.
Were there any difficulties?
I used to be a believer in fortune-telling, so words are difficult.
I thought it was difficult for me, too.
I had to speak very fast because I was so excited, and I had to speak very fast.
There was one time I chewed a lot.
What was it?
This sharp middle looking a thousand miles ahead is surely not the key point here yet.
I couldn't come up with the key point.
I couldn't say the key point, and after a while I kept saying keep in, keep in, keep in, keep in, keep in, keep in, keep in.
And for about that many seconds in real life.
I thought I had a bug.
It became funny to me as I said it.
The key point.
The keypoints, the peepoints, the peepoints, the peepoints.
They were all different.
Nonaka and Yuna were in the same space,
Everyone's faces were all staring at each other.
They were trying to hold back their laughter for a moment.
It was bad, wasn't it?
Yes, I had already done it.
That was the best.
That was funny.
It was fun.
But it's still fun.
Everyone says "Pinkle-chan," but that's just Pinkle-chan, isn't it?
I'm sorry, my slur is bad.
Pinkle. Pinkle.
Is that you?
Pinkle-chan.
Pinkledee.
Pinkle.
Yu is the one who skipped a line.
When Yuu skipped a line,
He said he remembered that he was in trouble.
I remembered.
Surprise.
But...
She's usually covering it up.
It's cute, isn't it?
So honest.
You must have been in a hurry.
I remembered.
You were surprised, weren't you?
Riko, what did you draw for Emma every time?
That's right.
Emma asked me for my autograph, like, "I'm a writer, can I have your autograph? She asked me for my autograph,
I said, "Sure,
I said yes, and I would draw something,
I wanted to make Emma laugh every time,
I drew really weird illustrations.
That's right.
Emma and I were saving them.
Did you air them all?
I don't know if she just threw it away.
She said something like, "I've got it all on film.
I don't know what it says,
I don't know what it says, but it's a signature. He drew a picture of himself.
Toward the end?
The whole time.
Emma's?
Various. Her face is thin.
I see.
She did all kinds of illustrations.
There were many places to show off my work,
I couldn't handle it all in one go.
That's true.
I don't think I had enough eyes.
It's a contrast of our differences.
To the girl who said she'd love to go to a friend or something,
Then I said I'd love to go,
I told them it's more of a comedy than a stage show,
That's true. Contrast.
Yes, that's right.
Like this?
I was looking at the menu, and there was something that looked delicious.
Actually, what's on that menu,
It's all shrimp dishes, and it says "bar" on it,
Shrimp cocktails, you know,
And then there were deep-fried shrimp,
Shrimp cakes, and everything else,
The staff made about 20 kinds of pictures,
It was all very handmade.
That's right.
How did you feel when Emma hit you?
Me? She hit me too.
You know. I was like, "I wouldn't mind being hit by Emma.
The part where Emma punched me was so well received that it was very difficult to write the rest of the dialogue.
It was a big hit.
It was like Emma was going to hit me.
Yes, it was.
Something like that?
Thank you very much for coming.
Thank you very much.
What would you like to talk about next?
What do you think?
Please vote again!
Was it a low-cost restaurant?
I mean, why wouldn't it be? Nobody ordered anything.
All they ordered was, uh...
and oolong tea?
No one ordered anything.
Well, I guess I'd better go.
Five, four, three, two, one, done!
What did they pick?
Number two!
Number two?
We're about to go on tour!
I can't talk about number one.
Oh, no.
I'm going to finish in about 2 minutes.
To be honest, the set list is here.
It's here.
I think there are quite a lot of setlists.
It's fun.
It's a tour that pulls down the Indigoa album,
But that's not all,
There are songs from the past as well as some shocking songs,
If you are familiar with this album, of course you should listen to the album,
If you are familiar with this album, I hope you will listen to the album, and if you also listen to the past songs of Ebichu, I feel that you will probably enjoy them.
I don't have enough material to spoil it.
Honestly.
But I'm putting out a video of Rokuware Art's call now,
I want you to remember that.
I think Rocware Art is going to be a big hit,
It's very difficult, but we didn't think you'd make a big rap,
I guess it's the Umeda Cypher in town.
It's a rap with a lot of love from Kenny Raz,
I'm practicing.
Isn't it amazing that I managed to remember it?
It's amazing.
The costumes this time were based on the ideas of the members,
We discussed with each other about the colors and patterns to be used for the costumes,
It's not finished yet,
Please look forward to it.
So, that's all for now,
That's all for now.
What are you looking forward to? This time.
There are some things I can't say.
There are some things I can't say, but I'm looking forward to seeing them,
Where will it be?
But we're going to be going quite a bit this time, aren't we?
I'm going from Sapporo to Fukuoka.
I want to eat a lot.
A lot is fun.
That's fun too.
Well, let's continue.
That's it.
I said it's over,
It's over.
Let's move on.
Thank you.
Okay. Please.
Please.
Please vote.
What's the set-up like? I don't know yet.
It's true that only China is coming. This time.
Hand-tightening decision, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1,
Start!
What was chosen?
Are they asking all the questions from the top?
Sure.
It could be anything.
Vertical?
Let's talk about everything today.
Okay, let's talk about family.
I'm going to Nakayama now.
I'm a blonde,
I only have online stories from yesterday.
But most of them said, "How long are you going to stay blonde? I'm sure.
Indeed.
You know the two-shot session at the album scoring session?
Everyone probably wants to be photographed with blonde hair.
I understand. It would sell like hotcakes.
That's what I'm saying,
I'm graduating from blonde hair.
It's already shorter than it used to be.
Yes, yes, yes.
It really hurts. High tones.
That's why I cut it off too,
It was longer,
It's going to break before you know it.
After one break, I noticed about 3 days later that the work was already done and it was amazing.
Even though it was short.
High tones are hard work. Really.
I was supposed to wear my hair blonde only during the album release period,
But I wore my hair blonde on stage as well, and Mr. Tsuchiya said he liked it that way, so I extended the blonde hair,
I extended my blonde hair, and also my black hair.
I extended my blonde hair, but I also have black hair,
You can cut your hair, can't you?
I think April 7 is the first day of the nickname.
If I had blonde hair there and black hair later, I wouldn't like that either.
I don't want to be photographed as a blonde, only to be photographed with a darker hair color the next time,
What is the next number you want to be?
I haven't decided yet.
But once I get this far out, I can get into pretty much anything.
But it won't be gold anymore.
But I would like to do it again someday if I have the chance.
It's a tough situation. The high-tone situation is really tough.
You've been using a high tone for a long time, haven't you, Mei-chan?
That's true. I had blonde hair first and then pink, right?
That's right.
That's why I had it all the way here,
And then you realized it was short?
I noticed it was getting more and more messed up.
The music video for "Crystal Drop" was really short and my hair was pink,
Then it was totally different before and after.
It was almost like my friends would say, "Did you get a wolf cut? I had extensions and arranged my hair in a way that it looked like a wolf cut,
I had my hair extensions mixed in with the hair arrangement,
It was a lot of work.
Hair care was hard.
The makeup artist told me to cut the video that day,
I told the principal and cut it two days later.
When I realized it, it was short.
But it's cute.
It's so much fun.
It's going to be short for a while.
Except for black, it's pink.
Pink. If you make it pink...
It's hard to get the color in.
If it's pink like mine, it's still good,
But the reddish color stays. It's not so bad.
It leaves in an instant,
That's right.
The girl's dividend itself is difficult, isn't it?
Why don't we go with light blue? Because... Isn't that too much to ask?
Light blue... no?
How about blue hair? She said...
Blue hair. Blue.
Pink? Like it looks black?
I'm going to look like a cartoon character.
I'm sure of it.
So, I'm happy to report that I will be graduating from blonde hair in a little while.
It's March. It's graduation season.
So, next time, it might really be just a live FC event.
Thank you very much.
If you were able to see me, it means that you are very rare.
See you soon.
That's all for now.
Let's continue.
Continue,
What are you asking for?
Maybe next time,
Miru-chan?
Yes. I'm asking for a favor.
Are we done?
Okay, five, four, three, two, one, done!
What was chosen?
I don't know.
Number 4.
I think we should start from the top.
This is so cool.
That's enough.
Okay, okay. Just go from the top.
Okay. I can't have hay fever,
You already know that, don't you?
Isn't it bad?
Who's that?
I'm sure you know who it is,
Is this the center of the building two years ago?
It was like this,
Breathing in the pollen from the chichu.
It's really bad.
It's me and Hinoki right now.
The tree of the day was starting,
And the make-up artist who did my make-up during the shrimp show at the theater is really cute, isn't she?
And Taniki, too.
But she always talks so much.
Hoshinomi, it's about time the sun tree started.
She really is.
She's really giggly.
And she has a stuffy nose all the time. I can tell.
I've been feeling a bit fuzzy around here all the time,
It's like there's a tree of the sun or something here,
It's like a forest around my face,
It's really painful. It's really painful.
I need your help.
I don't have pollen, but I don't have a runny nose or eyes,
My skin is rough.
It's really bad.
I heard it's really bad this year.
I want the same as Misato,
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Stop it.
It's really bad.
I recommend the Caspican yogurt.
Which one?
It's yogurt.
I recommend the Kai of the Nose.
Nose Kai is highly recommended by the geographical institute school I go to.
I know some of the Ebi students had hay fever when I was on stage,
So the nasal spray is different depending on the mood of the audience.
The microphone is attached here, so if you blow your nose, it gets into the microphone.
That's right.
Nothing works.
I heard there is a cure for hay fever. Is it cured?
I think Mr. P.E. got cured.
Is that possible?
What was it?
He said he was cured by eating yogurt.
He wrote about it on Twitter.
Is it true?
He says it's good to heal from the inside of the intestinal environment,
He really says that.
I drink it every day,
What do you think?
Mr. P.E., send me more of that yogurt as soon as possible.
What kind of yogurt is that?
Someone got cured with Caspican.
Really? Really?
I told you that there are people who are asking for information,
I heard that there's some kind of allergy tolerance system that you can build up by putting allergy ingredients in your body all the time,
But if you start at this time of the year, it's very hard to do.
It would take about 3 years to build up a tolerance,
That's crazy.
But even if it takes 3 years, it might be good for the rest of my life.
That's right. I think it might be better if I think about my life from now on.
There are so many this year.
I got better when I got older.
Oh, really?
On the contrary.
I don't have it now, but fall is coming.
Fall is bad. Autumn is bad.
Both are bad.
Both of them.
I heard that one time the treatment for the end-of-life treatment is going to be a really big café tea.
That's bad.
I can't talk.
I know when I'm drowning.
I get all boha-boha.
Let's get through this spring together, café-tea people.
Let's do our best.
We have allies here. Thank you very much.
Sorry I can't be your ally.
I'm the only one.
Okay, then. Is this number 5?
Let's go to number 5.
White rice is too delicious,
I never used to eat that much white rice.
I used to eat it when I was little,
But I haven't been eating it recently,
I have an image of having to endure it.
But...,
But last year, I tried to eat white rice,
I tried eating white rice,
I realized how delicious it was,
I finally became a Japanese?
Yes. I finally became Japanese,
And natto on rice.
Natto on rice, not natto-tamayaki rice?
And you wrote something about your goals for this year.
Did you write anything down?
QR?
It was on a public radio recording,
I want to eat.
Like, I want to eat a lot.
He wrote that.
I've been saying that for a long time.
But it's really too delicious,
I've been eating a lot lately.
I did a survey of 50 people,
Three hundred?
If you get one, you're out.
If one person sits down, he or she is out.
It's like the person who ate the natto-tamayaki rice,
Everyone disappeared.
That's true.
Not everyone eats natto tamayaki gohan.
But the natto tamayaki gohan looks delicious.
It's so delicious, I'm crazy about it.
It's like, "I'm addicted to natto, so I'm going to eat it.
But natto and egg yolk as it is,
You know the ones they sell with the egg yolk on the lid?
I do.
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's so good.
I know.
Now there's a kind of natto that tastes like plums,
It's so delicious.
The black soybean natto is delicious, and the black soybean natto has sansho (Japanese pepper) on it.
Absolutely delicious.
Omotsume's natto.
I want to eat natto.
I can already smell natto now.
Natto, I can eat natto with rice,
But there are people who put natto in pasta or omelette.
Who can eat natto?
Yes, I can. Not at all.
Yes, I can.
Last time I ate okonomiyaki with natto.
Is that normal?
Maybe not for me.
I don't like natto to get warm.
Does anyone understand?
Yes, I do.
Natto with curry, too,
No?
Warm, warm, warm, warm.
Natto in a cup of ramen tastes great.
No?
It's hot natto.
It's so delicious.
That's right.
Nakamoto's cup ramen.
Reri and Ren were planning to eat it with me,
I told her what toppings to put on it,
She recommended what toppings to put on it,
I'm not a big fan of warm natto, even more than spicy.
I can't do it.
My senior said it was delicious.
You know, natto is good in golden tanmen.
But the rice is also warm.
You don't like natto warm?
That's right. Natto itself should not be warm.
I really want you to try it. It is really delicious.
I was knocked down once, so eat it.
It was really delicious.
I'll try it.
Please do.
I'll tell you what I think.
That's what she said.
At the end, Mi-chan chatted with us.
I'm curious about this.
I'm curious about this one. Please talk to me at the end.
Lately, I used to be a talker, but I've become more talkative,
That's true.
Yes, that's right.
During the theater sleep,
I was thinking,
I think I mentioned earlier that the make-up artist is also chatty,
She was talking all the time there, too,
But she was talking all the time, and I was cross-talking with Masai who was doing makeup on the other side of the room,
It was very noisy in the dressing room,
Once I was feeling a little sick,
Today, I was in a daze,
It's so quiet backstage.
It's so quiet.
And then I was told, "The dressing room is so quiet when Mi Yu-chan is not talking.
I was told, "You're so quiet backstage when you're not talking," or something like that,
There were 10 members and make-up artists in the dressing room,
I was surprised,
I was surprised.
I guess I was starting to feel like a neighborhood old lady.
Shut up.
It's so noisy.
She was on a roll. Mi Yu.
I got a sore throat.
I'm thirsty from all the talking.
Isn't it great before the show?
Lately, my friends are talking a lot.
It's amazing how much they talk and talk and talk.
I'm so thirsty,
I haven't had a drop of alcohol,
It's a private room, so it's okay,
I was laughing all the time.
She was able to give Mi-chan back to him in about an hour and a half.
That was amazing.
Moreover, Mariya has been talking a lot lately.
That's right.
She talks a lot.
You could live in Osaka.
No, I can't live there.
I can't live in Osaka,
I don't really know the definition of cheerful and gloomy.
Besides, my friends from school are very solid,
I don't think they are that cheerful.
Surprisingly calm?
She came to see me on stage,
He was really dressed up.
I was surprised.
He came to a very beautiful room because he was told it was a stage,
I thought, "Wow!
But the content changed a lot,
I thought, "Oh wow, he came in a very beautiful room just because he was told to go on stage,
I thought, "Thank God I have friends.
I hear people who don't know the definition of the word "jolly".
No, no, no, no.
Isn't it the yin cans who define it?
There are yin cans who can say that.
I understand.
There are those who specialize in what they like and talk a lot.
They are wonderful friends.
She asked me if someone could take a video of her backstage,
Oh, that's not true at all.
If it was a surprise or something,
I'm afraid that if it were filmed as a surprise or something, I'd get a lot of spiky talk from everyone.
That's right. Spiky talk.
Really.
That's right. It was interesting.
Yes, it was. I guess so.
Mai and I are stacking the volume surprisingly high,
Maybe they are. You mentioned that earlier.
But it's amazing, isn't it? You know the stage was about a week long, right?
The whole time.
That's right. Everyone was talking during the free time.
We had a lot of free time, about 3 hours.
We talked for 2 or 3 hours during the free time.
Even when I was sleepy, they were talking all the time.
And even in the year of retirement, everyone was talking together.
It was interesting.
It's like that.
I'll talk. But I want to refrain a little bit and go to the spirit.
Please stay like this.
Yes, sir. So that's that,
You're not good at pretending, are you?
That's all for now.
Next is a project like this.
A pleasant and fun March.
For the rest of the month, I'd like to do some March-like projects.
There was a theme,
I don't have to introduce all of them,
What do you want to do?
What do you have in mind? What do you want to do?
This is the best one, right?
Okay, theme.
Hay fever project.
Project. Research the cutest sneeze in the world.
You're cute just the way you are, aren't you, Sei-chan?
My sneeze is something I say to myself,
I'm told it's cute.
I can't say anything. It's so cute.
What's it like?
I don't know. I don't know,
Like a little girl.
The rest of him is cute.
That's right.
Like a hyuu.
My friends say I'm an idol only because of my sneeze.
She really is an idol.
Only sneezing is an idol.
My special skill,
Oh, no.
I have to study how to sneeze.
Well, Rikko is silent.
That's right. I can do a silent sneeze.
And I'm not the only one.
Rika-chan says she can do it, too.
Both of us,
That's right. Shoe doesn't come out either.
It's like when I'm in a situation where I really shouldn't sneeze right now,
She tries her best. Silently.
I can't do it.
I might have done it on stage, too.
Isn't it amazing?
It doesn't come out.
If it's there,
I would.
I'd like to know.
I'm pretty much a four!
I get a lot of attention.
It's hard.
Who can do that? Silent sneeze.
I think I did it onstage.
I'm doing it with a microphone right here.
I think he did it.
Convenient. Really.
But I don't think it's a skill.
If you let it out as hard as you can, it's another sneeze.
No, it's not.
You have to study how to make a cute sneeze.
I wonder.
Let's do a little bit of what I think is a cute sneeze.
Cushion.
It's no good.
How will it end? I can't see the end.
Cushion. Wow, I saw the cushion.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
How'd it go? How'd it go?
How's it look?
Good?
Please Sayuri.
Sayuri, please... and when Sayuri came, she said I shouldn't sneeze because I'd really sneeze.
She said it's not cute.
It's not cute.
Then, just say "booshan" like a normal person.
Then you can just try harder, right?
Okay. Let's go with that.
Do it like this.
Wouldn't it be cute if you did it like that?
What? Boshan.
Yeah. Isn't it cute?
It's not cute at all.
It feels better to sneeze as hard as you can.
That's true.
Let her do it freely.
And there's always the silent Rikawa-chan.
Wouldn't it be nice if she stopped sneezing?
I wonder.
Sayuri, please.
Hencho.
Kuhyun
sneeze sneeze
sneeze sneeze sneeze
How's it going?
How's it going? They're making me say "sneeze.
Oh.
It's okay.
It's not good to start singing at the end of a sentence.
It's fine as it is.
Then sneeze all you want.
Okay, let's move on.
Top theme.
I wonder what it is.
Speeches to send to graduates.
I may send to the graduates.
I'll give a speech.
What do you mean?
Like, to the graduating class.
Like you were the principal.
Do you want a double principal or a solo principal?
Let's go with the double principal.
Maybe we can make it a unique school. Two principals.
Thank you all for coming to today's graduation ceremony of Aibi Private School.
Thank you very much.
With the principal, Mirei Hoshino,
I am Riko Nakayama.
We have an unusual system here at Miyako Gakuen where we have two principals,
I know this is a long speech, but I would like to convey my thoughts and feelings to our graduates.
Spring has come, hasn't it?
Spring has come. It's graduation season.
Are you aware of the fact that you are going to be stripped of your uniform?
The sleeves were long when you were in the first year of junior high school, but now they are too short and you have become adults.
Your future is limitless.
It's not over yet.
Fly to the future!
Go for it!
Congratulations on your graduation!
This is Riko Nakayama, principal, and
and Mirei Hoshida, our principal.
We will continue to serve as principals next year as well.
Now, if you will excuse me.
Excuse me.
Yes, so it was a rare occasion.
Do you have any memories of the graduation ceremony?
Graduation ceremony memories?
I didn't have a graduation ceremony at Corona. Like when I was in college.
That's right. It was when I entered the Corona Disaster,
I could still wear hakama,
But there was no graduation ceremony, and the institute was mailed to me, so I had the most unresidential graduation ceremony.
But I'm still thankful that I was able to get together with my friends,
Maybe that's my favorite memory of the graduation ceremony.
I don't think I have ever cried at a graduation ceremony.
I don't know what it was like, but it didn't make me cry?
You didn't cry?
Maybe I haven't cried much.
No kidding?
You probably didn't cry in kindergarten, right?
I don't remember much. I didn't cry in elementary school either.
I didn't cry much either, but in elementary school.
Isn't it difficult to be in a mood where you have to cry?
When everyone around you is crying and you feel like you have to cry too,
I yawn desperately to get the tears out.
Can you give me some advice?
But in elementary school, when I was in shape, a current student played some song on the recorder,
I don't remember it at all.
Didn't you do something like that in elementary school or something, like a degreaser? The graduation ceremony.
I did.
That was me, Yusuke's Sunflower,
We danced Sunflower and Onna-igi Defective,
I feel the time period. Now.
I'm sure.
I don't remember the song.
I don't remember the song, but it was moving.
It was moving.
I don't know the song,
I was moved, but I don't think I cried.
But it's strange, isn't it? When you grow up, it's different,
You see people you meet at all. Friends from school.
I see friends from elementary school, junior high school, and college,
But it is only as students that we have the space to say goodbye, as if we will never see each other again.
Are there graduation ceremonies for integrated junior and senior high schools?
Yes, there is.
There was one, but it was very quick and easy.
I see.
It's like, "Next year will be easy anyway.
Next month anyway.
There's a crash, though.
There was a girl crying.
That's right.
Of course there are.
On the day of departure, the day of departure? It's a good song, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Can you sing it? What song am I singing?
It's a good song.
It's time to say goodbye.
Time to go.
Let's leave.
Believe in the future.
Believe with bouncing young power.
This wide, this wide, this wide, this wide.
Great song!
I'm in.
I think it's strange to sing in a chorus when you become an adult.
There are a lot of strange things that I think about when I grow up.
What's in the free talk?
Isn't the chorus so strange?
I think there must be someone who made it right,
This heroine, this heroine,
Joyful, Mr. Tatake, the creature attendant.
Goodbye, sadly...
Yale.
I always wondered about the bottom alto part of Yale.
What's it like?
Good-bye is not sad.
La la la la la la la. We connected.
Like a yell.
I don't feel like I'm being yelled at at all.
Yale.
I thought it was very strange.
That's strange, isn't it?
He said it was strange to write each other's words.
It was fun.
Field trip.
Digging for potatoes with everyone.
The first overnight school stay in the second grade.
The campfire we all watched together.
Indeed.
All are happy memories.
Nostalgic.
After this culture, though,
I think I'll be like I'm actually a kid or something and I'll be able to sing this stuff.
Yeah.
It's already the ending.
I buried the size capsule.
I'm curious about the size capsule.
I didn't receive it, and I'm sure they do it every year.
I'm sure they dig them up.
What do you think? My elementary school teacher told me.
I'm sure there's no place to bury them.
I'm supposed to open it for my coming-of-age ceremony when I turn 20,
But because of the Corona disaster, it's buried forever.
I thought I buried mine in a tree in the schoolyard of my elementary school,
I wonder where it went.
I'm sure it's not there.
That's right.
I want that letter back.
I want it. I want it back.
Is there a generation that's doing it and a generation that's not doing it?
Is that so?
The time capsule was ruined by the rain. It looks the saddest.
I want it. I want what I buried.
I don't remember what I buried.
That's what's interesting, but I have to dig it up.
I want it.
I want to get this to someone else's teacher. This thought.
I wonder if they'll dig it up in, like, 3,000 years and be like, "What's this?
I'm sure they will.
I think it will be a cultural link.
I guess I'm done now.
The ending.
It was a happy and fickle March.
Now, it's the end of the 67th edition of Ebichu's Delightful and Funny Showroom.
Announcement.
Jangan!
15th Anniversary Tour 2024 The Other Side of Indigo Hour
We are going to do it.
There are still some things that are not yet known, so we are waiting for the spring tour without any announcement.
So, I know it's a bit of a balance.
I just had a thought, and it goes back to the time capsule,
If someone had put a pocket car in a time capsule, it is likely that the pocket car would be very expensive when it is dug up.
That's likely.
There was a person who had put Yu-Gi-Oh in a time capsule, and I thought, "Poof!
It's possible.
Do you have a dream?
Yes, I do.
It's possible, isn't it?
Like the appearance of a high-priced Pokécar.
Then, what are the top five in the final ranking?
Starting from No. 5, right?
Fifth.
A little bit of a watch.
It's a clock on a clock.
Oh, here it comes. Here it comes.
Fifth place.
Sunrise monk.
Thank you.
4th place. Mr. Clone 12.
Thank you very much.
3rd place. Mr. Air.
2nd place. Ms. Matcha.
Thank you very much.
First place. Ms. Tamapin.
Yes. That concludes the 67th edition of Ebichu's Delightfully Furufuru Showroom.
The next installment will be announced as soon as it is decided.
That's all for now.
What?
A mystery you want to know about.
That's all for now.
This is the mystery you want to know about.
Bye-bye.
I talked a lot.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching.